# **ARTYOM ZAGOSKIN**

## iOS Developer

in https://linkedin.com/in/artyomzagoskin



https://github.com/Inxel



artyzago@gmail.com

Open-minded, flexible, mindfulness, collaborative iOS developer with 3+ years of experience. Participate in all phases of development: system design, UI and UX discussion, decomposition and development. Spending spare time exploring new technologies to use it in pet and work projects. Fascinated about my job.

### **LANGUAGE**

#### **English**

Professional Working Proficiency

#### Russian

Native

### **CERTIFICATES**

### iOS Development

Napoleon IT Course 2019

#### FCE (CEFR Level - B2)

Cambridge University Press 2019

### **SKILLS**

- Swift
- SwiftUI
- Multi-threading
- · Object-Oriented Programming
- Protocol-Oriented Programming
- Collaboration
- Communication
- Time management
- · Agile and Scrum workflow
- · JIRA / Confluence / Git

### **EDUCATION**

### **Computer and Information Sciences**

2017 - 2021

South Ural State University

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### iOS Developer

**2021 - present** 

**Aviasales** 

- Worked with results page (results showing 1.5x faster) and ticket screen
- Develop hotel page (75% more bookings)
- Make UI with SwiftUI (previously UIKit without storyboards)
- Objective-C to Swift refactoring
- Work in team of 4 iOS developers
- MVVM architecture
- Code review
- Unit and snapshot tests

### iOS Developer

2019 - 2021

Napoleon IT

- 1. Retail app:
  - · Clean Swift (VIP) architecture
  - Worked in team of 2 iOS developers
- Developed catalog, authorization, shop cart, etc.
- 2. Platform for local services and specialized jobs:
  - VIPER architecture
  - Worked with GoogleMaps and other frameworks
  - Developed profile, task creating constructor, transactions history, etc.
  - Localization
- Only one iOS developer
- 3. Initialization of app (MWVM + Coordinators).
- 4. Mentor.
- 5. Lecturer of Napoleon IT iOS course.